[{"answer": "Fine.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "I should plug your book because otherwise there isn't any reason you have to come out, isn't it?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "I am a uniter.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "How can you say that with a straight face?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "But finally it explodes.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Did you get the tweeted picture?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I was definitely too nice to Hillary Clinton.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Maybe I could've cared in there in a bit just calm things a bit and been less polarizing?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "But you never supported Chris Christie?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I just told you.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "I mean do you have feelings like Glenn Beck?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Are there any times you've gone too far?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "You don't think you've ever gone too far?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "I am being totally ...", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "But what do you say -- let's try to be serious for a moment, right?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I am not -- you're part of the problem.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "... part of the problem, right?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "OULTER: Well, no.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "I mean is it almost exactly the same thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "My point is you're never going to get a scandal against the Democrat broken by MSNBC.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "What's your point?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "I think it's the most boring scandal of my entire life.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "What do you think of the Chris Christie scandal so far?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "That I am massively opposed to Chris Christie because he had his temporary sent an appointee, vote for amnesty.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "... is not a very serious story?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "I don't think he was electable.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Is that helpful to the GOP's chances of beating Hillary Clinton if she runs in 2016?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I'm totally against the legalization of pot and not one of these it should be legal for adults but not for kid.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "Thoughts?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "During -- well I'm going through it.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Which word isn't true in all that is said?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "First.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What isn't true?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "That ...", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What part of the word he said is not true?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "The incarceration figures is -- are ridiculous because 90 percent of those are plea bargain, they catch the guys with six kilos of heroin will plea bargain you down to pot.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Or the fact that it's no more dangerous scientifically?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "And that -- well I keep trying to when you keep interrupting.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Why do you keep saying that's untrue and not explain why?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "I'm drunk right now.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Are you intoxicated now?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Wait.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Have you ever smoked pot?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "No, I haven't.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Have you ever smoked pot?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Almost none of my friends have because their athletes.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Never in your life?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "And interrogate (ph) a lot of them -- well look potheads can still get the pot they're probably self medicating.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "How many potheads do you know?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "Because potheads are incapable of following simple instructions and getting a job done.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Why, why for commerce?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Was when I move to a new place in California and there was a pool and the pool guy didn't, you know, I come back then it's four feet down it's color covered with green mold.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "But would be mean by pothead?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Everyone knows what a pothead is.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "What do you mean by a pothead?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Its' not smoking pot one time.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "What is it mean?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Enough.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "So how much are you assuming a pothead takes?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "No heavy smokers work all night and then die young saving the Social Security System money.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "So like a heavy drinker or a heavy smoker?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, everything dies eventually.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "You accept that people can overdose on too much alcohol?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Is he right?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "You wouldn't take issue with that?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "I'm just saying, if you care about the productivity...", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "So, you would rather they would chain smoking and heavy drinking?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Some people are addict.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "One cigarette or two?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "She's from Texas.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "That's hilarious but could we also point out that the first e-mail you read during the break was from your publicist telling you let her talk, huh?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "I love Texas.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "Are you dissing the entire State of Texas right now?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Does he know the NRA is not a person and cannot have been born.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "So what do you make of Harvey Weinstein making a stand against the NRA?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "Yes, OK, give the money back.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What is wrong with people?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Because it's utter hypocrisy otherwise.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "Why would that make anything better?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "You're absolutely 100 percent wrong.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Look, people -- countries are different, demographics are different.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "How do you explain that you have similar percentages of a population who are believed to have some form of mental illness in the UK, in Australia, in Japan, in Germany, and yet because there is no availability of guns, they do not have the gun violence?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "It's been one of the most -- I'm producing all the years of my whole career.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Ozzy, what are the moments for you to get back with Sabbath to have this album to come out?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Don't be ridiculous.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "What was the last meal you cook, Sharon?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "It is special and its well-deserved too, you know, my goodness and they've all paid their dues over and over and over again.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "Pretty special, right?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Well ...", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "What went on there Ozzy?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "Well, it's out of my control.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "How did you feel when you watched that Ozzy?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "It was more hurt.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "Did you fear that this might end the marriage?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "I can't say -- I can't ...", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "Do you think you'll be able to avoid falling off the rails again?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "I cannot say yes and I can't say no because it's cunning, powerful, and bad because my head will say, \"Gone.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 734, "question": "Or this is going to live with you forever, do you think?", "qSentId": 733}, {"answer": "Well, It was very difficult, she was really upset with me, you know, and I don't blame her.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "How did you were back?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "Ozzy came around to have a talk at the hotel that I was staying at and I told him -- no, I was like.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "What was that?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "You know what, it's -- you put up this front because it's what you should do.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 764, "question": "What was the moment for you Sharon when you thought, \"I'm going to take him back\"?", "qSentId": 763}, {"answer": "You know, I think that some of it is just his age.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "What's going on with young Mr. Bieber?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "We did the quivering myth.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 821, "question": "I mean it's just incredible that he did so well, right?", "qSentId": 820}, {"answer": "She is.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 838, "question": "But Kelly is like a mini me, isn't she really?", "qSentId": 837}, {"answer": "It's up in the air.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 850, "question": "Are you going to carry on new gadgets and stones in the '70s?", "qSentId": 849}, {"answer": "Oh my gosh, you're going everywhere.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 852, "question": "I'm going for it but what we all doing we're going to do a tour of -- where am I?", "qSentId": 851}, {"answer": "It was great better than ever.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "You still get on together as family?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "I think it's great.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 872, "question": "As a huge Beatles fan, what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 871}, {"answer": "But I can remember the first time I heard \"She Loves You\", I was looking in -- my when I listened and I asked him with the transistor and I heard \"She Loves You\".", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 878, "question": "Amazing isn't it?", "qSentId": 877}, {"answer": "Amazing.", "docId": "140122pmt", "aSentId": 881, "question": "That's great song, didn't it?", "qSentId": 880}]